## Sakshi Shukla

Machine Learning Engineer and Writer

### Summary

I am an inquisitive person who wants to know the why of everything. Also I believe creativity comes from within. I love learning new foreign languages French, German etc. I love listening to various speeches and dlivering them out myself as well. Also I love researching new topics which give out new challenges and help usto find new solutions of it. Formerly I was an intern at Gspann Technologies.

#### Experience

Co-Founder at Devorbs August 2017 - Present

Intern at GSPANN Technologies, Inc June 2017 - Present

Member

2017 - Present

Member

2017 - Present

Trainer at British Council

2011 - 2015 (5 years)

Awarded as Gold Awardee, Silver Awardee for the IAYP group which is an International Award for Young People held by British Council

Instructor at The International Award for Young People

2011 - 2015 (5 years)

A Gold Awardee

Trainee at Alliance Française de Delhi

November 2012 - October 2014 (2 years)

Dance Instructor at DANCEWORX ACADEMY LIMITED

2010 - 2014 (5 years)

Cadet at NATIONAL CADET CORPS - India

2011 - 2013 (3 years)

# Education

Bharati Vidyapeeth college of engineering, New Delhi Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology, 2015 - 2019 St. Mary's School Safdarjung Enclave Computer Science, 2002 - 2015 Goethe Max Mueller Bhavan

# Sakshi Shukla

Machine Learning Engineer and Writer



Contact Sakshi on LinkedIn